CURRICULUM VITAE

Jimoh Adams Eniola

E-mail Address: ghostintime.a@gmail.com

Phone: 09026661157

Summary

Jimoh Adams Eniola, a BSC holder in Mass Communication from Elizade University, Ilara Mokin, Ondo State. I had my NYSC program at the Consumer Affairs Department of the Nigerian Communication Commission (NCC). I have garnered experiences from internship programs from different organizations such as Cool FM where I worked directly under the Video Editor, assisted in editing videos. I also worked at News Agency of Nigeria (NAN) where I wrote news stories, features, conducted vox pops, transcribed and edited audio works.

A high performing individual with an exemplary attitude; impeccable integrity; and professionalism, demonstrating drive, enthusiasm and initiative, with the ability to consistently deliver on record time, improve my skill, broaden my horizon and accurately ensure that i contribute to the continuous growth and development of the organization. From the acquired experience during my internship and NYSC program respectively, it is certain that I would perform excellently at any given task.

EDUCATION AND PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

PRIMARY SCHOOL LEAVING CERTIFICATE.

BEST SCHOOL INTERNATIONAL, ABUJA (2004 – 2009)

JUNIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

SAPATI INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, KWARA STATE (2010 – 2016)

WEST AFRICA EXAMINATION COUNCIL CERTIFICATE

SAPATI INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, KWARA STATE (2016)

TERTIARY EDUCATION (B.SC DEGREE)

ELIZADE UNIVERSITY, ONDO STATE (2016 – 2020)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

COOL FM: Oct – Nov (2017)

Sourcing for news, news stories, information and public opinion.

Conducting vox pop, airing people's opinion as regards pressing and general issues.

Writing of news, articles, news stories, citations etc.

NEWS AGENCY OF NIGERIA: August – Oct. (2018)

Taking care of studio equipment.

Taking records of every equipment taken out for gigs, jobs, lent out.

Receiving clients warmly and attending to them.

Good handling of camera

Conducting vox pops

NIGERIA COMMUNICATION COMMISSION

(**YOUTH CORPER**): April 2021 – February 2022

Filing of documents.

Registering documents, submission of files and docs.

Writing, registration and submission of memos.

NATIONAL ASSEMBLY

PERSONAL ASSISTANT: MARCH 2022 – NOVEMBER 2022

Liaising with internal department

Answering calls and making travel arrangement

Typing of memos

Taking messages

NATIONAL COMMISSION OF MUSEUM AND MONUMENT

HERITAGE OFFICER: NOVEMBER 2022 – 2023

Research work using archives

Filing of internal and external memos

SKILLS

Communication Skills

Team work

Proficient use of Microsoft Office

Transcribing skill

Good listening skill

Editing skill

Research Skill

VOLUNTEER

Nigeria Red Cross Society

Date: Mar. 2021 – February 2022

Position: Volunteer (DB – 123/FCT)

Haven life foundation-Date: March 2021 – February 2022

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

Nigerian Institute of Public Relations

Date: 2021

Ultimate Public Relations Masterclass, Udemy

Date: 2022

REFERENCES

1) Prof. M.B Olayiwole

5 Abakaliki Street, Gwarinpa estate

Abuja

Tel: 08033229532

2) Alhaji Fatai O. Jimoh

Deputy Clerk, House of Representatives

National Assembly

Abuja

Tel: 08035075000

3) Mrs Thompson Olatige Taiwo

Matron

State House Medical Clinic

Tel: 08057750170